

Hi! I'm SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Adejumo Oreoluwa

adejumooreololuwa@gmail.com

www.mavipopdigitals.com

Determined Software Developer offering more than 4 years of expertise in fast-paced departments. Bilingual and well-spoken with the ability to work closely with people of all different backgrounds and personalities. Seeking an opportunity to oversee a team of exceptional in a well established company.

WORK EXPERIENCES

01

Sep 2022 - Present

LEAD WEB DEVELOPER

WebEdge Services - Lagos

- Troubleshooting of technical issues to solve problems within a reasonable time frame.
- Utilized frameworks like Flutter, WordPress, HTML, CSS and JavaScript

Mav 2018 – Present

CTO

Mavipop Digitals - Abeokuta

- Led the team to develop websites and web applications for clients all over the world.
- Utilized programming capabilities in PHP, SQL, JavaScript and Flutter and other libraries as needed.

L.

LEAD WEB DEVELOPER

Becadel Solutions - Lagos

- Redesigned Website to increase traffic, applying SEO techniques to improve google ranking.
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages and sites for continuous improvement.



Phone

Address

+2349036727573 4, Surulere Street, Camp, Abk.

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

02

- UI/UX Design
- Website Optimisation
- WordPress
- PHP/OOP
- HTML/CSS/JS
- Flutter
- Dart
- SEO

EDUCATION

03

Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta

2018 - 2023

BSC: Agricultural & Bio-Resources Engineering

Baptist Boys' High School, Oke-Saje 2014-2017

Certificate of Higher Education: Science

HOBBIES

04







Singing

Designing

Photography

CERTIFICATES

05

Nova University

2020

Certificate of Completion, Web design

Side Hustle

2022

Certificate of Completion, Mobile App Development